A Finding Aid to the Leo Castelli Gallery Records, circa 1880-2000, bulk 1957-1999, in the Archives of American Art AAA.leocast
Archives of American Art
- Artists Files, 1913-1999, bulk 1960s-1990s; Series 4; (Boxes 57-133, 197-208, OVs 242-243; 89.5 linear feet)
  - Photographs, 1913-1998; 4.2
    - Artschwager, Richard, 1965; (Oversized material from Box 102, Folder 5) (Box 207, Folder 2)
    - Bardon, Marcel - Press Photos, 1976; (Oversized material from Box 104, Folder 2) (Box 207, Folder 3)
    - Charlton, Alan - Press Photos, 1971; (Oversized material from Box 105, Folder 24) (Box 207, Folder 4)
    - Chryssa, 1979-1988; (Oversized material from Box 106, Folder 6) (Box 207, Folder 5)
    - Cohen, Mark - Press Photos, 1974-1979; (Oversized material from Box 106, Folder 10) (Box 207, Folder 6)
    - di Berluis, 1976; (Oversized material from Box 108, Folder 1) (Box 207, Folder 7)
    - Feldstein, Mark - Patrick [Castelli's Dog], 1977; (Oversized material from Box 108, Folder 14; Filed at bottom of box due to size) (Box 207, Folder 8)
    - Feldstein, Mark - Press Photos, circa 1975-1978; (Oversized material from Box 108, Folder 14) (Box 207, Folder 9)
    - Flavin, Dan, circa 1970s-1990s; (Oversized material from Box 108, Folder 21) (Box 207, Folder 10)
    - Fotographien Aus Berlin (Exhibition) - Press Photos, circa 1980-1984; (Oversized material from Box 108, Folder 27) (Box 207, Folder 11)
    - Gibson, Ralph - Press Photos, 1973-1979; (Oversized material from Box 109, Folder 3) (Box 207, Folder 12)
    - Gossage, John, 1974-1978; (Oversized material from Box 109, Folder 7) (Box 207, Folder 13)
    - Jenshel, Len - Press Photos, 1976-1979; (Oversized material from Box 110, Folder 1) (Box 208, Folder 1)
    - Mark, Mary Ellen - Press Photos, circa 1977; (Oversized material from Box 117, Folder 12) (Box 208, Folder 2)
    - Namuth, Hans, circa 1960s; (Oversized material from Box 118, Folder 17) (Box 208, Folder 3)
    - Namuth, Hans - Performance Art, circa 1960s; (Oversized material from Box 118, Folder 18) (Box 208, Folder 4)
    - Oldenburg, Claes, circa 1970s-1990s; (Oversized material from Box 120, Folder 9) (Box 208, Folder 5)
    - Rauschenberg, Robert, 1955-1964; (Oversized material from Box 121, Folder 17) (Box 208, Folder 6)
    - Rosenquist, James, circa 1970s-1980s; (Oversized material from Box 123, Folder 18) (Box 208, Folder 7)
    - Serra, Richard, circa 1969-1980; (Oversized material from Box 126, Folder 13) (Box 208, Folder 8)
    - Simonds, Charles, circa 1970s-1980s; (Oversized material from Box 127, Folders 9-10) (Box 208, Folder 9)
    - Stella, Frank, circa 1959-1970; (Oversized material from Box 129, Folder 4) (Box 208, Folder 10)
    - Stella, Frank - BMW, 1976; (Oversized material from Box 130, Folder 4) (Box 208, Folder 11)
    - Tomkins, Spencez, 1974; (Oversized material from Box 130, Folder 21) (Box 208, Folder 12)
    - Unidentified Artists, circa 1950s-1990s; (Oversized material from Box 131, Folder 7) (Box 208, Folder 13)
    - Warhol, Andy, circa 1960s; (Oversized material from Box 132, Folder 1) (Box 208, Folder 14)
    - Warhol, Andy [oversized], 1972; (Oversized material from Box 132, Folders 4-5) (Box 208, Folder 15)
    - Lichtenstein, Roy - Comic Strip, circa 1960s-1990s; (Oversized material from Box 116, Folder 16) (Box OV 243)
    - Rosenquist, James, circa 1960s-1990s; (Oversized material from Box 123, Folder 18) (Box OV 242)
    - Scarpitta, Salvatore, circa 1960s-1990s; (Oversized material from Box 126, Folder 4) (Box OV 242)
    - Serra, Richard, circa 1970s-1980s; (Oversized material from Box 126, Folder 13) (Box OV 243)
    - Unidentified Artists, circa 1970s-1980s; (Oversized material from Box 131, Folder 7) (Box OV 242)
- Printed Materials, 1949-1998; Series 5; (Boxes 134-153, 209-211, OVs 244-274, 276, 300; 18.6 linear feet)
  Printed materials are a rich resource of information about the history of the gallery, information about Leo Castelli, and the gallery's significant role in the contemporary art world. Materials include exhibition announcements, flyers, invitations, magazine articles and clippings, newspaper clippings, press releases, and many exhibition posters representing a visual exhibition history of the gallery.
  The series is arranged as 4 subseries:
  5.1: General Archives, 1949-1998
  5.2: Leo Castelli, 1951-1998
  5.3: Subject Files, 1963-1995
  5.4: Posters, 1959-1997
  - General, 1949-1998; 5.1
    This subseries contains exhibition announcements, flyers, invitations, magazine articles and clippings, newspaper clippings, and press releases from the Leo Castelli Gallery and other galleries and museums. The materials document the exhibition history of the gallery, Leo Castelli and his artists, and other art-related topics of interest to the gallery.
    - General Archives (1949) (Box 134, Folder 1)
    - General Archives (1957-1959) (Box 134, Folder 2)
    - General Archives (undated), circa 1960-1969; (Oversized material housed in Box 209, Folder 1) (Box 134, Folder 3)
    - General Archives (1960) (Box 134, Folder 4)
    - General Archives (1961) (Box 134, Folder 5)
    - General Archives (1962), (Oversized material housed in Box 209, Folder 2) (Box 134, Folder 6)
    - General Archives (1963), (2 folders; Oversized material housed in Box 209, Folder 3) (Box 134, Folder 7-8)
    - General Archives (1964), (3 folders; Oversized material housed in Box 209, Folder 4) (Box 134, Folder 9-11)
    - General Archives (1965), (2 folders; Oversized material housed in Box 209, Folder 5) (Box 134, Folder 12-13)
    - General Archives - Frederick Kiesler (1965) (Box 134, Folder 14)
    - General Archives (1966), (3 folders; Oversized material housed in Box 209, Folder 6) (Box 134, Folder 15-17)
    - General Archives (1967), (3 folders; Oversized material housed in Box 209, Folder 7) (Box 134, Folder 18-20)
    - General Archives (1968), (2 folders; Oversized material housed in Box 209, Folder 8) (Box 134, Folder 21-22)
    - General Archives (1969), 1968-1969; (3 folders; Oversized material housed in Box 209, Folder 9) (Box 135, Folder 1-3)
    - General Archives (1969) (Box 135, Folder 4)
    - General Archives (1970), (4 folders; Oversized material housed in Box 209, Folder 10) (Box 135, Folder 5-8)
    - General Archives (1971), (4 folders; Oversized material housed in Box 209, Folder 11) (Box 135, Folder 9-12)
    - General Archives (1972), 1971-1972; (Oversized material housed in Box 209, Folder 12) (Box 135, Folder 13)
    - General Archives (1972), 3 Folders (Box 135, Folder 14-16)
    - General Archives (1973), 1972-1974; 3 Folders (Box 135, Folder 17-19)
    - General Archives (1973), 1972-1974; (3 folders; Oversized material housed in Box 209, Folder 13) (Box 136, Folder 1-3)
    - General Archives (1974), (4 folders; Oversized material housed in Box 209, Folder 14) (Box 136, Folder 4-7)
    - General Archives (1975) (Box 136, Folder 8)
    - General Archives (1975-1), 5 Folders (Box 136, Folder 9-13)
    - General Archives (1975-2), 4 Folders (Box 136, Folder 14-17)
    - General Archives (1976) (Box 136, Folder 18)
    - General Archives (1976), (4 folders; Oversized material housed in Box 209, Folder 15) (Box 137, Folder 1-4)
    - General Archives (1977-1), 1976-1977 (Box 137, Folder 5)
    - General Archives (1977-1), 3 Folders (Box 137, Folder 6-8)
    - General Archives (1977-1), 1977-1978 (Box 137, Folder 9)
    - General Archives (1977-2), 1976-1977 (Box 137, Folder 10)
    - General Archives (1977-2), (4 folders; Oversized material housed in Box 209, Folder 16) (Box 137, Folder 11-14)
    - General Archives (1978-1), (3 folders; Oversized material housed in Box 209, Folder 17) (Box 137, Folder 15-17)
    - General Archives (1978-2), 1977-1978; 2 Folders (Box 137, Folder 18-19)
    - General Archives (1978-2), (Oversized material housed in Box 209, Folder 18) (Box 137, Folder 20)
    - General Archives (1978-2) (Box 138, Folder 1)
    - General Archives (1978-2), 1978-1979; (Oversized material housed in Box 209, Folder 18) (Box 138, Folder 2)
    - General Archives (1979), (6 folders; Oversized material housed in Box 210, Folder 1) (Box 138, Folder 3-8)
    - General Archives (1980), (6 folders; Oversized material housed in Box 210, Folder 2) (Box 138, Folder 9-14)
    - General Archives (1981) (Box 138, Folder 15)
    - General Archives (1981-1), 4 Folders (Box 138, Folder 16-19)
    - General Archives (1981-1), (2 folders; Oversized material housed in Box 210, Folder 3) (Box 139, Folder 1-2)
    - General Archives (1981-2), (3 folders; Oversized material housed in Box 210, Folder 4) (Box 139, Folder 3-5)
    - General Archives (1982-1), (4 folders; Oversized material housed in Box 210, Folder 5) (Box 139, Folder 6-9)
    - General Archives (1982-2), (3 folders; Oversized material housed in Box 210, Folder 6) (Box 139, Folder 10-12)
    - General Archives (1983-1), 2 Folders (Box 139, Folder 13-14)
    - General Archives (1983-1), 1983-1985; 3 Folders (Box 139, Folder 15-17)
    - General Archives (1983-2), 3 Folders (Box 139, Folder 18-20)
    - General Archives (1983-2), 3 Folders (Box 140, Folder 1-3)
    - General Archives (1984-1), 5 Folders (Box 140, Folder 4-8)
    - General Archives (1984-2), (2 folders; Oversized material housed in Box 210, Folder 7) (Box 140, Folder 9-10)
    - General Archives (1984-2), 1985; (3 folders; Oversized material housed in Box 210, Folder 8) (Box 140, Folder 11-13)
    - General Archives (1985), (Oversized material housed in Box 210, Folder 9) (Box 140, Folder 14)
    - General Archives (1986), (Oversized material housed in Box 210, Folder 10) (Box 140, Folder 15)
    - General Archives (1986-1), (4 folders; Oversized material housed in Box 210, Folder 11) (Box 140, Folder 16-19)
    - General Archives (1986-1) (Box 141, Folder 1)
    - General Archives (1986-1987), 3 Folders (Box 141, Folder 2-4)
    - General Archives (1987-1), (5 folders; Oversized material housed in Box 210, Folder 12) (Box 141, Folder 5-9)
    - General Archives (1987-2), (4 folders; Oversized material housed in Box 210, Folder 13) (Box 141, Folder 10-13)
    - General Archives, 1988 (Box 141, Folder 14)
    - General Archives (1988), (5 folders; Oversized material housed in Box 210, Folder 14) (Box 141, Folder 15-19)
    - General Archives (1989), 1988; 2 Folders (Box 141, Folder 20-21)
    - General Archives (1989), (3 folders; Oversized material housed in Box 210, Folder 15) (Box 142, Folder 1-3)
    - General Archives (1990), 5 Folders (Box 142, Folder 4-8)
    - General Archives (1990-2), 1989; 2 Folders (Box 142, Folder 9-10)
    - General Archives (1990-2), 3 Folders (Box 142, Folder 11-13)
    - General Archives (1990-1991), 1989-1990; (Oversized material housed in Box 210, Folder 16) (Box 142, Folder 14)
    - General Archives (1990-1991), 3 Folders (Box 142, Folder 15-17)
    - General Archives (1991), (Oversized material housed in Box 210, Folder 17) (Box 142, Folder 18)
    - General Archives (1991), (3 folders; Oversized material housed in Box 210, Folder 18) (Box 143, Folder 1-3)
    - General Archives (1992), (5 folders; Oversized material housed in Box 210, Folder 19) (Box 143, Folder 4-8)
    - General Archives (1993) (Box 143, Folder 9)
    - General Archives (1993-1), 1992-1993; 5 Folders (Box 143, Folder 10-14)
    - General Archives (1993-2), 5 Folders (Box 143, Folder 15-19)
    - General Archives (1993-2.2), 5 Folders (Box 144, Folder 1-5)
    - General Archives (1993-4), (3 folders; Oversized material housed in Box 210, Folder 20) (Box 144, Folder 6-8)
    - General Archives (1994-1), 3 Folders (Box 144, Folder 9-11)
    - General Archives (1994-2), (6 folders; Oversized material housed in Box 210, Folder 21) (Box 144, Folder 12-17)
    - General Archives (1994-3), (6 folders; Oversized material housed in Box 210, Folder 22) (Box 145, Folder 1-6)
    - General Archives (1994-4), (Oversized material housed in Box 210, Folder 23) (Box 145, Folder 7)
    - General Archives (1995-1), (4 folders; Oversized material housed in Box 210, Folder 24) (Box 145, Folder 8-11)
    - General Archives (1995-2), (6 folders; Oversized material housed in Box 210, Folder 25) (Box 145, Folder 12-17)
    - General Archives (1995-3), 2 Folders (Box 145, Folder 18-19)
    - General Archives (1995-3), 3 Folders (Box 146, Folder 1-3)
    - General Archives (1996), 6 Folders (Box 146, Folder 4-9)
    - General Archives (1997), 1996-1997; (5 folders; Oversized material housed in Box 210, Folder 26) (Box 146, Folder 10-14)
    - General Archives (1997) (Box 146, Folder 15)
    - General Archives (1998) (Box 146, Folder 16)
    - General Archives (undated), circa 1960-1969; (Oversized material from Box 134, Folder 3) (Box 209, Folder 1)
    - General Archives (1962), (Oversized material from Box 134, Folder 6) (Box 209, Folder 2)
    - General Archives (1963), (Oversized material from Box 134, Folder 7) (Box 209, Folder 3)
    - General Archives (1964), (Oversized material from Box 134, Folder 9) (Box 209, Folder 4)
    - General Archives (1965), (Oversized material from Box 134, Folder 12) (Box 209, Folder 5)
    - General Archives (1966), (Oversized material from Box 134, Folder 16) (Box 209, Folder 6)
    - General Archives (1967), (Oversized material from Box 134, Folder 18) (Box 209, Folder 7)
    - General Archives (1968), (Oversized material from Box 134, Folder 22) (Box 209, Folder 8)
    - General Archives (1969), (Oversized material from Box 135, Folder 2) (Box 209, Folder 9)
    - General Archives (1970), (Oversized material from Box 135, Folder 7) (Box 209, Folder 10)
    - General Archives (1971), (Oversized material from Box 135, Folder 10) (Box 209, Folder 11)
    - General Archives (1972), (Oversized material from Box 135, Folder 13) (Box 209, Folder 12)
    - General Archives (1973), 1973-1974; (Oversized material from Box 136, Folder 3) (Box 209, Folder 13)
    - General Archives (1974), (Oversized material from Box 136, Folder 6) (Box 209, Folder 14)
    - General Archives (1976), (Oversized material from Box 137, Folder 2) (Box 209, Folder 15)
    - General Archives (1977-2), (Oversized material from Box 137, Folder 14) (Box 209, Folder 16)
    - General Archives (1978-1), (Oversized material from Box 137, Folder 17) (Box 209, Folder 17)
    - General Archives (1978-2), (Oversized material from Box 137, Folder 20; Box 141, Folder 2) (Box 209, Folder 18)
    - General Archives (1979), (Oversized material from Box 138, Folder 7) (Box 210, Folder 1)
    - General Archives (1980), (Oversized material from Box 138, Folder 14) (Box 210, Folder 2)
    - General Archives (1981-1), (Oversized material from Box 139, Folder 1) (Box 210, Folder 3)
    - General Archives (1981-2), (Oversized material from Box 139, Folder 5) (Box 210, Folder 4)
    - General Archives (1982-1), (Oversized material from Box 139, Folder 9) (Box 210, Folder 5)
    - General Archives (1982-2), (Oversized material from Box 139, Folder 11) (Box 210, Folder 6)
    - General Archives (1984-2), (Oversized material from Box 140, Folder 10) (Box 210, Folder 7)
    - General Archives (1984-2), 1985; (Oversized material from Box 140, Folder 13) (Box 210, Folder 8)
    - General Archives (1985), (Oversized material from Box 140, Folder 14) (Box 210, Folder 9)
    - General Archives (1986), (Oversized material from Box 140, Folder 15) (Box 210, Folder 10)
    - General Archives (1986-1), (Oversized material from Box 140, Folder 17) (Box 210, Folder 11)
    - General Archives (1987-1), (Oversized material from Box 141, Folder 8) (Box 210, Folder 12)
    - General Archives (1987-2), (Oversized material from Box 141, Folder 12) (Box 210, Folder 13)
    - General Archives (1988), (Oversized material from Box 141, Folder 16) (Box 210, Folder 14)
    - General Archives (1989), (Oversized material from Box 142, Folder 3) (Box 210, Folder 15)
    - General Archives (1990-1991), (Oversized material from Box 142, Folder 14) (Box 210, Folder 16)
    - General Archives (1991), (Oversized material from Box 142, Folder 18) (Box 210, Folder 17)
    - General Archives (1991), (Oversized material from Box 143, Folder 2) (Box 210, Folder 18)
    - General Archives (1992), (Oversized material from Box 143, Folder 7) (Box 210, Folder 19)
    - General Archives (1993-4), (Oversized material from Box 144, Folder 7) (Box 210, Folder 20)
    - General Archives (1994-2), (Oversized material from Box 144, Folder 15) (Box 210, Folder 21)
    - General Archives (1994-3), (Oversized material from Box 145, Folder 5) (Box 210, Folder 22)
    - General Archives (1994-4), (Oversized material from Box 145, Folder 7) (Box 210, Folder 23)
    - General Archives (1995-1), (Oversized material from Box 145, Folder 10) (Box 210, Folder 24)
    - General Archives (1995-2), (Oversized material from Box 145, Folder 16) (Box 210, Folder 25)
    - General Archives (1997), 1996-1997; (Oversized material from Box 146, Folder 10) (Box 210, Folder 26)
  - Leo Castelli, 1951-1998; 5.2
    Found here is printed materials focusing on Leo Castelli and his role at the gallery and in the art world through magazine and newspaper articles, newsletters, invitations, exhibition posters and announcements, transcripts, and memorabilia such as matchbooks with Leo Castelli's photograph printed on them. Of interest are parts of a personal memoir manuscript edited by Leo Castelli.
    - Leo Castelli, 1951-1966; (2 folders; Oversized material housed in Box 211, Folder 1) (Box 146, Folder 17-18)
    - Leo Castelli (undated), circa 1960s-1990s (Box 146, Folder 19)
    - Leo Castelli (undated) - Matchbooks, circa 1960s (Box 146, Folder 20)
    - Leo Castelli, 1967-1968 (Box 146, Folder 21)
    - Leo Castelli, 1969-1971; (Oversized material housed in Box 211, Folder 2) (Box 146, Folder 22)
    - Leo Castelli, 1971-1973 (Box 147, Folder 1)
    - Leo Castelli, 1974-1976 (Box 147, Folder 2)
    - Leo Castelli, 1976-1977; (Oversized material housed in Box 211, Folder 3) (Box 147, Folder 3)
    - Leo Castelli, 1977; 2 Folders (Box 147, Folder 4-5)
    - Leo Castelli, 1978-1979; (Oversized material housed in Box 211, Folder 4) (Box 147, Folder 6)
    - Leo Castelli (1978-1980) (Box 147, Folder 7)
    - Leo Castelli (1978-1980), 1978-1979 (Box 147, Folder 8)
    - Leo Castelli (1978-1980) (Box 147, Folder 9)
    - Leo Castelli (1981-1982) (Box 147, Folder 10)
    - Leo Castelli (1981-1982), (2 folders; Oversized material housed in Box 211, Folder 5) (Box 147, Folder 11-12)
    - Leo Castelli (1983-1984), 2 Folders (Box 147, Folder 13-14)
    - Leo Castelli (1983-1984), 2 Folders (Box 147, Folder 15-16)
    - Leo Castelli (1985-1986) (Box 147, Folder 17)
    - Leo Castelli (1985-1986) (Box 147, Folder 18)
    - Leo Castelli (1985-1986), 2 Folders (Box 148, Folder 1-2)
    - Leo Castelli (1987-1), 3 Folders (Box 148, Folder 3-5)
    - Leo Castelli (1987-2), 3 Folders (Box 148, Folder 6-8)
    - Leo Castelli (1987-3), 4 Folders (Box 148, Folder 9-12)
    - Leo Castelli - Matchbooks, 1987 (Box 148, Folder 13)
    - Leo Castelli, 1988 (Box 148, Folder 14)
    - Leo Castelli (1988), (3 folders; Oversized material housed in Box 211, Folder 6) (Box 148, Folder 15-17)
    - Leo Castelli (1988-1989), 2 Folders (Box 148, Folder 18-19)
    - Leo Castelli (1988-1989), 3 Folders (Box 149, Folder 1-3)
    - Leo Castelli (1989), 1989-1990; (2 folders; Oversized material housed in Box 211, Folder 7) (Box 149, Folder 4-5)
    - Leo Castelli, 1990 (Box 149, Folder 6)
    - Leo Castelli (1990), 3 Folders (Box 149, Folder 7-9)
    - Leo Castelli (1991-1), 1990-1991; 5 Folders (Box 149, Folder 10-14)
    - Leo Castelli (1991-2), 2 Folders (Box 149, Folder 15-16)
    - Leo Castelli (1992-1), 1991-1992; (4 folders; Oversized material housed in Box 211, Folder 8) (Box 149, Folder 17-20)
    - Leo Castelli (1992-1), 1991-1992 (Box 150, Folder 1)
    - Leo Castelli (1992-2), 1991-1992; (4 folders; Oversized material housed in Box 211, Folder 9) (Box 150, Folder 2-5)
    - Leo Castelli, 1993-1994 (Box 150, Folder 6)
    - Leo Castelli (1993-1), 5 Folders (Box 150, Folder 7-11)
    - Leo Castelli (1993-2), 1993-1994; (3 folders; Oversized material housed in Box 211, Folder 10) (Box 150, Folder 12-14)
    - Leo Castelli (1994-1) (Box 150, Folder 15)
    - Leo Castelli (1994-1), 1994-1995; 2 Folders (Box 150, Folder 16-17)
    - Leo Castelli (1994-2), 1994-1995; (3 folders; Oversized material housed in Box 211, Folder 11) (Box 150, Folder 18-20)
    - Leo Castelli (1994-2), 1994-1995; 2 Folders (Box 151, Folder 1-2)
    - Leo Castelli (1995), 3 Folders (Box 151, Folder 3-5)
    - Leo Castelli (1996) (Box 151, Folder 6)
    - Leo Castelli (1996), 1996-1997 (Box 151, Folder 7)
    - Leo Castelli, 1997-1998 (Box 151, Folder 8)
    - Leo Castelli, 1962-1966; (Oversized material from Box 146, Folder 17) (Box 211, Folder 1)
    - Leo Castelli, 1970; (Oversized material from Box 146, Folder 22) (Box 211, Folder 2)
    - Leo Castelli, 1976; (Oversized material from Box 147, Folder 3) (Box 211, Folder 3)
    - Leo Castelli, 1979; (Oversized material from Box 147, Folder 6) (Box 211, Folder 4)
    - Leo Castelli (1981-1982), (Oversized material from Box 147, Folder 12) (Box 211, Folder 5)
    - Leo Castelli (1988), (Oversized material from Box 148, Folder 16) (Box 211, Folder 6)
    - Leo Castelli (1989), (Oversized material from Box 149, Folder 5) (Box 211, Folder 7)
    - Leo Castelli (1992-1), (Oversized material from Box 149, Folder 18) (Box 211, Folder 8)
    - Leo Castelli (1992-2), (Oversized material from Box 150, Folder 3) (Box 211, Folder 9)
    - Leo Castelli (1993-2), (Oversized material from Box 150, Folder 13) (Box 211, Folder 10)
    - Leo Castelli (1994-2), 1994-1995; (Oversized material from Box 150, Folder 19) (Box 211, Folder 11)
  - Subject Files, 1963-1995; 5.3
    Subject files contain clippings, flyers, magazines and books, and other printed material compiled by the gallery on topics related to artists, the art world, or other general art-related interests. Folders are arranged alphabetically by subject, then chronologically within the folder.
    - 65 Thompson Street, 1989-1990 (Box 151, Folder 9)
    - 65 Thompson Street, 1990-1992 (Box 151, Folder 10)
    - 142 Greene Street, 1980-1981 (Box 151, Folder 11)
    - 142 Greene Street, 1992, 1995 (Box 151, Folder 12)
    - 578 Broadway Exhibitions - Mike Bidlo, 1988 (Box 151, Folder 13)
    - "Architecture I", 1977-1978 (Box 151, Folder 14)
    - "Architecture II", 1978-1981; (Oversized material housed in Box 211, Folder 12) (Box 151, Folder 15)
    - "Architecture II" - News Clippings, 1980 (Box 151, Folder 16)
    - "Architecture II" - Press Releases, Invitations, 1980 (Box 151, Folder 17)
    - "Architecture III: Follies", 1977, 1983-1984 (Box 151, Folder 18)
    - "Architecture III" - Press Kit for Barbara Jakobson, 1983 (Box 151, Folder 19)
    - Art Tower Mito, 1991 (Box 151, Folder 20)
    - Auctions, 1985, 1988-1991 (Box 151, Folder 21)
    - Auctions, 1991; 2 Folders (Box 152, Folder 1-2)
    - Auctions, 1991-1992 (Box 152, Folder 3)
    - Auctions - Clippings, 1991-1992 (Box 152, Folder 4)
    - Auctions - Directors, Curators, Dealers, 1987-1990 (Box 152, Folder 5)
    - Auctions - Directors, Curators, Dealers, 1990-1991; (Oversized material housed in Box 211, Folder 13) (Box 152, Folder 6)
    - Auctions - Directors, Curators, Dealers, 1991 (Box 152, Folder 7)
    - Auctions - Directors, Curators, Dealers (Clippings), 1989-1991 (Box 152, Folder 8)
    - Auctions - Larry Gagosian, 1989-1992 (Box 152, Folder 9)
    - Castelli, Toiny, 1987-1988; (Oversized material housed in Box 225, Folder 14) (Box 152, Folder 10)
    - Collectors, 1963-1969; (Oversized material housed in Box 211, Folder 15) (Box 152, Folder 11)
    - Collectors, 1970-1978 (Box 152, Folder 12)
    - Collectors, 1980-1983 (Box 152, Folder 13)
    - Collectors, 1984-1985 (Box 152, Folder 14)